<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo on </title>
    <link>/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 20:08:19 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Quick Start</title>
      <link>/posts/hugo-quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 20:08:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hugo-quick-start/</guid>
      <description>Step 1: Install Hugo Homebrew, a package manager for macOS, can be installed from brew.sh. See install if you are running Windows etc.
brew install hugo  To verify your new install:
hugo version  Step 2: Create a New Site hugo new site quickstart  The above will create a new Hugo site in a folder named quickstart.
Step 3: Add a Theme See themes.gohugo.io for a list of themes to consider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Hugo Post</title>
      <link>/posts/another-hugo-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 12:29:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/another-hugo-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;toml-yaml-json-oh-my&#34;&gt;TOML, YAML, JSON &amp;mdash; Oh my!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the nifty Hugo features we should cover: flexible configuration and front matter formats! This entry has front
matter in &lt;code&gt;toml&lt;/code&gt;, unlike the last one which used &lt;code&gt;yaml&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;json&lt;/code&gt; is also available if that&amp;rsquo;s your preference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Hugo!</title>
      <link>/posts/hello-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 12:19:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hello-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Hello from Hugo! If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this in your browser, good job! The file content/post/hello-hugo.md has been converted into a complete HTML document by Hugo. Isn&amp;rsquo;t that pretty nifty?
A Section Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple titled section where you can place whatever information you want.
You can use inline HTML if you want, but really there&amp;rsquo;s not much that Markdown can&amp;rsquo;t do.
Showing off with Markdown A full cheat sheet can be found here or through Google.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>/posts/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>